talkfree7.blogspot.com 2011-10-06

# Talkfree7 Privacy Policy | Free Call, VOIP, Skype, Android, IOS, Apps, Cell Phone

The privacy of our esteemed visitors to www.talkfree7.blogspot.com is important to us. 

At www.talkfree7.blogspot.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit www.talkfree7.blogspot.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

When you access Google services, Google servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Also, in order to protect you from fraud, phishing, and other misconduct, Google may collect information about your interaction with their services. Any such information we collect will only be used to detect and prevent fraud or other misconduct.

http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html

 **Interest-Based Advertising across Google Adsense Ads:**

Google Adsense serves ads as contextual and placement-targeted advertising on its publishers' sites and they may also serve Adsense contextual ads on Interest-Based Advertising across the Google Adsense on its publishers' sites/ blogs etc, and to achieve this Google may use / collect necessary data from the visitors of this blog,

Visitation information from my blogs may be used to help create interest categories.

https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=113771&sourceid=aso&subid=ww-ww-et-asui&medium=link

 **We do follow Google and Adsense all privacy policies:**

https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=100557

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

**Log Files:**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as BSNL or Tata Indicom), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use [third party advertisements](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) on www.talkfree7.blogspot.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing New Delhi real estate ads to someone in New Delhi, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **User Options for Cookie Management:**

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. Additionally you may visit those [third party vendor websites](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to opt out of cookies (if the vendor offers this capability). However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by www.JenSense.com
